{
    "subject": "resource/Apple_Inc.",
    "predicate": "property/keyPeople",
    "object": "resource/Luca_Maestri",
    "human_readable": "Apple Inc.'s key people include Luca Maestri.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.946624755859375,
            "question": "Is Luca Maestri associated with Apple Inc.?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8666513562202454,
            "question": "What is the role of Luca Maestri at Apple Inc.?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8290902376174927,
            "question": "Name a key person at Apple Inc."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.706913411617279,
            "question": "Who is Luca Maestri?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6216325759887695,
            "question": "What company does Luca Maestri work for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.46724534034729004,
            "question": "What is Apple Inc. known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.43967145681381226,
            "question": "Who are some other important figures at Apple Inc.?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3312035799026489,
            "question": "What industry does Apple Inc. operate in?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.30082061886787415,
            "question": "Can you give an example of a product made by Apple Inc.?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2400657832622528,
            "question": "Where is Apple Inc. headquartered?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Apple Inc.'s key people include Luca Maestri.",
            "html": "dbpedia_7226_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you give an example of a product made by Apple Inc.?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7226_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What industry does Apple Inc. operate in?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7226_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Who are some other important figures at Apple Inc.?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7226_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7226_1.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7226_126.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7226_130.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7226_35.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7226_52.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7226_54.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7226_6.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7226_68.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7226_83.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7226_95.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the structured JSON answer:\n\n```\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThis indicates that the triple \"Apple Inc.'s key people include Luca Maestri\" is supported by the provided context information. The documents mention several times that Luca Maestri serves as the chief financial officer (CFO) of Apple Inc., which confirms this triple."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provide multiple pieces of information that support the statement that Apple Inc.\u2019s key people include Luca Maestri. Specifically, several documents confirm his role as the Chief Financial Officer (CFO) of Apple Inc., highlighting his significant contributions and leadership position within the company."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Very Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}